Daniel Williams

Charlotte, NC 28209 704.953.9384 d.j.williams1218@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Senior Technical Support Analyst, versatile, reliable and efficient with 10+ years of experience providing excellent customer service and team training. Diversified skills include problem solving, documenting issues for resolution, meeting monthly goals and building and repairing computers.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

On Demand Courier Services, Charlotte, NC

Owner and Operator

April, 2017 - Present

- Multi-tasking in pressured and potential dangerous environment
- Flexibility to work for multiple partners nearly simultaneously
- Provided quality customer service through positive and professional interaction with customers in person or by phone

LPL Financial, Charlotte, NC

Senior Technical Support Analyst Technical Support Analyst

June, 2016 – April, 2017

November, 2014 – June, 2016

- Role model for consistent delivery of quality service to financial advisors.
- Excellent work ethic and attention to expeditious quality service which lead to being 6-month MVP for Frontline Technical Support.
- Expert in managing daily schedule and being reliable and on time.
- Provided effective training to analysts that improved service levels.

Talent Bridge USA, Charlotte, NC

Technical Support Analyst, LPL Financial

August, 2014 – November, 2014

• Worked as contingent worker for 3 months until hired permanently.

The Home Depot, Charlotte, NC

Freight Team Associate

March, 2008 – August, 2014

- Stocked merchandise onto shelves for customer availability.
- Provided outstanding customer service by identifying and satisfying their needs and wants.
- Provided on the job training for new Freight Team Associates.
- Stood in for the Supervisor on multiple occasions.
- Earned multiple employee rewards for excellent customer service and for getting things done.

Forever 21, Charlotte, NC Stock Associate

September, 2005 – December, 2006 September 2007 – December 2008 March 2011 – February 2012

- Drove sales by managing the execution of shipment processing, replenishment, signage, and markdown procedures
- Ensure a clean, safe and hazard-free shopping and working environment which includes maintaining the back of house standards to positively impact the Associate experience

EDUCATION

Bachelor of the Arts in Software Information Systems:

May, 2011

The University of North Carolina at Charlotte

Concentration: Business

CERTIFICATIONS AND SKILLS

Computer Skills: Knowledge of Microsoft Office, Windows 7/8.1/10, PHP and HTML